Guide to the Rice University James Addison Baker College Records, 1956-2020 UA 082
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series XX: Administrative Files, 1968-2013, 183378
  - Subseries C: 1980s, 183393
    - College Courses, 1987/1988; 183426 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Commencement, 1987/1988; 183427 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Shakespeare Week, 1987/1988; 183428 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Student Lists, 1987/1988; 183429 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Awards/Honors, 1988/1989; 183430 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Cabinet, 1988/1989; 183431 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Commencement, 1988/1989; 183432 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Shakespeare Week, 1988/1989; 183433 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Student Lists, 1988/1989; 183434 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Awards/Honors, 1989/1990; 183435 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Cabinet, 1989/1990; 183436 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Commencement, 1989/1990; 183437 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - O-Week, 1989/1990; 183438 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Shakespeare Week, 1989/1990; 183439 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Student Lists, 1989/1990; 183440 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Subseries D: 1990s, 183441
    - Associates, 1990/1991; 183442 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Awards/Honors, 1990/1991; 183443 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Cabinet, 1990/1991; 183444 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Commencement, 1990/1991; 183445 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Shakespeare Week, 1990/1991; 183446 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Student Lists, 1990/1991; 183447 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Awards/Honors, 1991/1992; 183448 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Commencement, 1991/1992; 183449 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Shakespeare Week, 1991/1992; 183450 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Student Lists, 1991/1992; 183451 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Awards/Honors, 1992/1993; 183452 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Commencement, 1992/1993; 183453 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Student Lists, 1992/1993; 183454 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Shakespeare Week, 1992/1993; 183455 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Awards/Honors, 1993/1994; 183456 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Cabinet, 1993/1994; 183457 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Commencement, 1993/1994; 183458 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Shakespeare Week, 1993/1994; 183459 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Student Lists, 1993/1994; 183460 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Awards/Honors, 1994/1995; 183472 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Cabinet, 1994/1995; 183473 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Commencement, 1994/1995; 183474 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Shakespeare Week, 1994/1995; 183475 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Student Lists, 1994/1995; 183476 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Awards/Honors, 1995/1996; 183477 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Commencement, 1995/1996; 183478 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Divisional Advising, 1995/1996; 183479 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Shakespeare Week, 1995/1996; 183480 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Student Lists, 1995/1996; 183481 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Associates, 1996/1997; 183482 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Athletes, 1996/1997; 183483 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Awards/Honors, 1996/1997; 183484 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Baker Night, 1996/1997; 183485 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Cabinet, 1996/1997; 183486 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Commencement, 1996/1997; 183487 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Convocation, 1996/1997; 183488 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - O-Week, 1996/1997; 183489 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Shakespeare Week, 1996/1997; 183490 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Student Lists, 1996/1997; 183491 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Associates, 1997/1998; 183679 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Awards/Honors, 1997/1998; 183680 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Baker Night, 1997/1998; 183681 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Cabinet, 1997/1998; 183682 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - College Courses, 1997/1998; 183683 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Commencement, 1997/1998; 183684 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Convocation, 1997/1998; 183685 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Divisional Advisors, 1997/1998; 183686 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Health Services, 1997/1998; 183687 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - O-Week, 1997/1998; 183688 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Shakespeare Week, 1997/1998; 183689 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Student Lists, 1997/1998; 183690 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Associates, 1998/1999; 183691 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Athletes, 1998/1999; 183692 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Awards/Honors, 1998/1999; 183693 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Cabinet, 1998/1999; 183694 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - College Courses, 1998/1999; 183695 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Commencement, 1998/1999; 183696 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Convocation, 1998/1999; 183697 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Dang, Von, 1998/1999; 183698 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Few's Farewell Party, 1998/1999; 183699 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Incoming Campus Letters, 1998/1999; 183700 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Invoices, 1998/1999; 183701 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - O-Week, 1998/1999; 183702 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Shakespeare Week, 1998/1999; 183737 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Student Lists, 1998/1999; 183738 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Associates, 1999/2000; 183739 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Athletes, 1999/2000; 183740 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Awards/Honors, 1999/2000; 183741 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Baker Night, 1999/2000; 183742 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Cabinet, 1999/2000; 183743 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - College Courses, 1999/2000; 183744 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Commencement, 1999/2000; 183745 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Convocation, 1999/2000; 183746 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Divisional Advising, 1999/2000; 183747 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Henning, Daniel, 1999/2000; 183748 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Incoming Campus Letters, 1999/2000; 183749 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - O-Week, 1999/2000; 183750 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Shakespeare Week, 1999/2000; 183751 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Student Lists, 1999/2000; 183752 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Subseries E: 2000s, 183753
    - Associates, 2000/2001; 183754 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Athletes, 2000/2001; 183755 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Awards/Honors, 2000/2001; 183756 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Baker Night, 2000/2001; 183816 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - College Courses, 2000/2001; 183817 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Commencement, 2000/2001; 183818 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Divisional Advising, 2000/2001; 183819 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Incoming Campus Letters, 2000/2001; 183820 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - O-Week, 2000/2001; 183821 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Shakespeare Week, 2000/2001; 183822 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Student Lists, 2000/2001; 183823 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Athletes, 2001/2002; 183824 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Associates, 2001/2002; 183825 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Awards/Honors, 2001/2002; 183826 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Baker Night, 2001/2002; 183827 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Cabinet, 2001/2002; 183828 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - College Courses, 2001/2002; 183829 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Commencement, 2001/2002; 183830 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Convocation, 2001/2002; 183831 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Divisional Advising, 2001/2002; 183832 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - O-Week, 2001/2002; 183833 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Shakespeare Week, 2001/2002; 183834 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Student Lists, 2001/2002; 183835 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Associates, 2002/2003; 183878 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Athletes, 2002/2003; 183879 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Awards/Honors, 2002/2003; 183883 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Cabinet, 2002/2003; 183885 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - College Courses, 2002/2003; 183886 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Commencement, 2002/2003; 183903 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Convocation, 2002/2003; 183904 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 2002/2003; 183905 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Divisional Advising, 2002/2003; 183906 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Incoming Campus Letters, 2002/2003; 183907 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - O-Week, 2002/2003; 183913 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Registrar, 2002/2003; 183914 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Shakespeare Week, 2002/2003; 183915 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Student Lists, 2002/2003; 183916 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Associates, 2003/2004; 183917 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Athletes, 2003/2004; 183918 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Awards/Honors, 2003/2004; 183919 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Cabinet, 2003/2004; 183920 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - College Courses, 2003/2004; 183921 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Commencement, 2003/2004; 183922 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Convocation, 2003/2004; 183923 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence (photographs), 2003/2004; 184400 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - O-Week, 2003/2004; 184401 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - The Quiñones' Party, 2003/2004; 184402 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Shakespeare Week, 2003/2004; 184403 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Student Lists, 2003/2004; 184404 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Associates, 2004/2005; 184405 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Athletes, 2004/2005; 184406 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Awards/Honors, 2004/2005; 184407 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Cabinet, 2004/2005; 184408 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - College Courses, 2004/2005; 184409 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Commencement, 2004/2005; 184410 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Convocation, 2004/2005; 184411 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Divisional Advising, 2004/2005; 184412 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - O-Week, 2004/2005; 184413 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Shakespeare Week, 2004/2005; 184414 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Student Lists, 2004/2005; 184415 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Associates, 2005/2006; 184416 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Athletes, 2005/2006; 184417 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Awards/Honors, 2005/2006; 184418 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Cabinet, 2005/2006; 184419 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Commencement, 2005/2006; 184420 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Convocation, 2005/2006; 184421 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Divisional Advising, 2005/2006; 184422 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - O-Week, 2005/2006; 184423 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Shakespeare Week, 2005/2006; 184425 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Student Lists, 2005/2006; 184424 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Associates, 2006/2007; 184426 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Athletes, 2006/2007; 184427 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Awards/Honors, 2006/2007; 184428 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Baker Night, 2006/2007; 184429 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Cabinet, 2006/2007; 184430 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - College Courses, 2006/2007; 184431 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Commencement, 2006/2007; 184432 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Convocation, 2006/2007; 184433 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Divisional Advising, 2006/2007; 184434 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - O-Week, 2006/2007; 184435 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Shakespeare Week, 2006/2007; 184436 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Student Lists, 2006/2007; 184437 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Associates, 2007/2008; 184438 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Athletes, 2007/2008; 184439 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Awards/Honors, 2007/2008; 184440 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Cabinet, 2007/2008; 184441 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - College Courses, 2007/2008; 184442 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Commencement, 2007/2008; 184443 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Convocation, 2007/2008; 184444 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Divisional Advising, 2007/2008; 184445 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - O-Week, 2007/2008; 184446 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Shakespeare Week, 2007/2008; 184447 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Student Lists, 2007/2008; 184448 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Associates, 2008/2009; 184449 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Athletes, 2008/2009; 184450 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Awards/Honors, 2008/2009; 184451 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Cabinet, 2008/2009; 184452 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - College Courses, 2008/2009; 184453 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Commencement, 2008/2009; 184454 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Convocation, 2008/2009; 184455 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Divisional Advising, 2008/2009; 184456 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - O-Week, 2008/2009; 184457 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Shakespeare Week, 2008/2009; 184458 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Somewhere Over the Rainbo-Week book, 2008/2009; 184459 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Student Lists, 2008/2009; 184460 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Associates, 2009/2010; 184461 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Athletes, 2009/2010; 184462 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Awards/Honors, 2009/2010; 184463 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Cabinet, 2009/2010; 184464 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - College Courses, 2009/2010; 184465 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Commencement, 2009/2010; 184466 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Convocation, 2009/2010; 184467 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Divisional Advising, 2009/2010; 184468 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - O-Week (CD), 2009/2010; 184469 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Shakespeare Week, 2009/2010; 184470 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Student Lists, 2009/2010; 184471 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Subseries F: 2010s, 184472
    - Associates, 2010/2011; 184474 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Cabinet, 2012/2013; 184475 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Shakespeare Week, 2012/2013; 184476 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Baker College Probation Status Report, 2011 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Subseries G: n.d., 184473
    - College Courses, n.d.; 184477 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Student Events, n.d.; 184478 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Series XXI: Photographs, Negatives, and Slides, 1958-2001, 184479
  - Associates, 1980s-2000s; 184481 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Baker College Meals and Masters' House, February 1958; 184482 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Beer Bike, 1995, 1998, 1999, 2002, n.d.; 184483 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1997 Slideshow, 184484 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - College Coordinator, 1995/1996; 184486 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Commencement, 1996, 2001; 184485 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - O-Week, 1991; 184487 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - O-Week, 1992; 184488 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - O-Week, 1996; 184489 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - O-Week, 1999; 184490 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - O-Week, 2000, 2000s; 184491 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Photo Album, 1994/1995; 184492 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Powderpuff, 1994-1995; 184493 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Rice campus, 1998, n.d.; 184494 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Rice Owls Football, 1994-1995; 184495 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Shakespeare Week, 1980, 1990s, 1992, 1995, 1996; 184496 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Shakespeare Week, 1996, 1997, 2000s, n.d.; 184497 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Student Life, 1992-1995; 184551 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Student Life, 1995; 184552 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Student Life, 1995; 184553 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Student Life, 1996-1998, 1990s, 2000; 184554 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Series XXII: Audio/Visual, 1996-2001, 184555
  - Unidentified (camcorder videocassette), n.d.; 184556 (Box 40)
  - Baker Shakespeare (2 Hi-8 camcorder video cassettes), 1997; 184557 (Box 40)
  - Beer Bike (Hi-8 camcorder video cassette), 1997; 184558 (Box 40)
  - Coalter, George Recital (Hi-8 camcorder video cassette), May 6, 1997; 184559 (Box 40)
  - O-Week (3 Hi-8 camcorder video cassettes), 1997; 184560 (Box 40)
  - Beer Bike, Commencement (Hi-8 camcorder video cassette), 1998; 184561 (Box 40)
  - Cabinet, Beer Bike Prep (Hi-8 camcorder video cassette), 1998; 184562 (Box 40)
  - Reunion (Hi-8 camcorder video cassette), 1998; 184563 (Box 40)
  - Baker 13 Senior Run, Parting Glass (Hi-8 camcorder video cassette), 1999; 184564 (Box 40)
  - Farewell Party for Joan and Arthur Few (Hi-8 camcorder video cassette), May 1, 1999; 184565 (Box 40)
  - O-Week (Hi-8 camcorder video cassette), 1999; 184566 (Box 40)
  - Parting Glass, Commencement (Hi-8 camcorder video cassette), 2000; 184567 (Box 40)
  - Parting Glass (Hi-8 camcorder video cassette), 2001; 184568 (Box 40)
  - Romeo and Juliet (VHS), 1995; 184569 (Box 40)
  - Much Ado About Nothing (2 VHS), 1996; 184570 (Box 40)
  - The Winter's Tale (VHS), 1997; 184571 (Box 40)
  - Udo Unplugged (VHS), 2001; 184572 (Box 40)
  - Senior Video (VHS), n.d.; 184573 (Box 40)
- Series XXIII: Photographs and Scrapbook
  - Beer Bike, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - O-Week, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2-3)
  - Scrapbook, 1997/1998 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Series XXIV: Digital Archive
  These items were downloaded from the Baker College Digital Archive Google Drive, converted to pdf files, saved to an internal server, and printed. The digital files will be kept until June 2017. After that, the digital files will be deleted, but the physical files will remain in the collection.
  - Sub-Series A: Adrian Yao, 2013-2014
    - Cabinet Agendas (Box 41, Folder 5-6)
    - External Vice President (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - President (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - State of Baker Addresses (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - President Adrian Yao files
  - Sub-Series B: Andrew Stout, 2014-2015
    - Beer Bike (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Cabinet Agendas (Box 42, Folder 3-4)
    - Executive Vice President (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - President (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Representatives (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - SA Senator (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Secretary (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - State of Baker Addresses (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - President Andrew Stout files
  - Sub-Series C: Digitzed documents, 1974-1977
    Contents include: pdf scans of Baker College documents including Baker Book and O-Week documents, constitutions and procedures, correspondence, minutes, and Vitis.
    - Baker Book and O-Week documents, 1974-1977
    - Constitution and procedures, 1976-1977
    - Correspondence, 1977
    - Minutes, 1974-1977
    - Vitis, 1974
- Series XXV: Cabinet Documents
  - Cabinet, 2011/2012 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Cabinet Minutes, 1994/1995 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Cabinet Minutes, 2001/2002 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Cabinet Minutes, 2002/2003 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Cabinet Minutes, 2005/2006 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Cabinet Minutes, 2006/2007 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Cabinet Minutes, 2007/2008 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Cabinet Minutes, 2008/2009 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Cabinet Minutes, 2009/2010 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Cabinet Minutes, 2011/2012 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Cabinet Minutes, 2012/2013 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Cabinet Minutes, c. 2000 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Constitution/By-Laws, c. 2000, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Secretary Notes, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Series XXVI: Baker Shakespeare
  - Baker Shakespeare (photographs), 1976-1977 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Baker Shakespeare, c. 1990 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Baker Shakespeare (photographs), 1994 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Baker Shakespeare (photographs), 1995 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Baker Shakespeare (photographs), 1997 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Macbeth, 2001 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Baker Shakespeare, 2011- (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Shakespeare Week, 1978/1979 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Shakespeare Week, 1986/1987 (Box 43, Folder 15)
- Series XXVII: Photographs, Negatives
  - Baker Shakespeare, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Baker Shakespeare, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Baker Shakespeare, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Baker Shakespeare, 2000 and 2005 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Hamlet, 2011
    Contenst include: Jpgs of the performance.
- Series XXVIII: Audio/Visual
  - King Lear (2 DVD), 2003 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - King Lear (2 VHS), 2003 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - As You Like It, 2010 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    Contents include: mp4 files of performance.
  - Hamlet, 2011-03-10
  - Hamlet, 2011-03-19
  - The Merchant of Venice, 2013-03-15
- Series XXIX: T-Shirts and Memorabilia, 1995-2007
  - Margaritaville T-Shirt, 1996 (Box 45, Item 1)
  - Margaritaville T-Shirt, 1997 (Box 45, Item 2)
  - Margaritaville T-Shirt, 2000 (Box 45, Item 3)
  - Margaritaville T-Shirt, 2001 (Box 45, Item 4)
  - Romeo and Juliet, 1995 (Box 45, Item 5)
  - Much Ado About Nothing, 1996 (Box 45, Item 6)
  - The Winter's Tale, 1997 (Box 45, Item 7)
  - Julius Caesar, 1998 (Box 45, Item 8)
  - The Merry Wives of Windsor, 2000 (Box 45, Item 9)
  - King Lear, 2003 (Box 45, Item 10)
  - Much Ado About Nothing, 2007 (Box 45, Item 11)
  - 25 Years of BakerShakespeare T-Shirt, 1995 (Box 45, Item 12)
  - Beer Bike T-Shirt, 1996 (Box 45, Item 13)
  - Highway to Hell - Beer Bike T-Shirt, 1997 (Box 45, Item 14)
  - Winnie The Brew - Beer Bike T-Shirt, 2002 (Box 45, Item 15)
  - Hell-O-Week T-Shirt, n.d. (Box 45, Item 16)
  - Mentos Week T-Shirt, 1998 (Box 45, Item 17)
  - UFO-Week T-Shirt, 1999 (Box 45, Item 18)
  - Powderpuff T-Shirt, 1990s (Box 45, Item 19)
  - Camo T-Shirt, 2000s (Box 45, Item 20)
  - T-Shirt, 2000s (Box 45, Item 21)
  - Baker 13 T-Shirt, 1999 (Box 45, Item 22)
  - R.A. Hat, n.d. (Box 45, Item 23)
- Series XXX: Baker Shakespeare addendum
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Addendum from two Acessions: 2019.UA088 and 2020.UA001
  - Design Notes (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Flyers, 1973-1994 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Photographs (See Note for specific plays) (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Henry IV (1), Love's Labour Lost (1), The Country Wife (1), Unidentified(1), Much Ado About Nothing (8), Baker Feast (5), Romeo and Juliet (1), Midsummer Night's Dream (2), Macbeth - 1982 (6), Macbeth - 1991 (7), Twelfth Night (1)
  - Much Ado About Nothing Scrapbook, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Press, 1976, 1986, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Production Notes: Costumes, Cast List, Receipts, etc. (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Programs / Playbills (Baker Shakespeare), 1976-2017, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Programs / Playbills (Other Productions) (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Promotional Materials: Article, Sketch, DVD (2008 Richard III) (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - T-shirts/Costumes
    - Winter's Tale, 1997 (Box 48)
    - King Lear, 2003 (Box 48)
    - The Tempest, 2009-03-19-2009-03-28 (Box 48)
    - Arsenic and Old Lace, n.d. (Box 48)
    - Hamlet, n.d. (Box 48)
    - Twelfth Night, 2002 (Box 48)
    - The Taming of the Shrew, 2005 (Box 48)
    - The Merchant of Venice, n.d. (Box 48)
    - The Merry Wives of Windsor, 2000 (Box 48)
    - Macbeth, n.d. (Box 48)
    - Much Ado about Nothing, n.d. (Box 48)
    - Much Ado About Nothing, 2007 (Box 48)
    - Romeo and Juliet, 2014 (Box 48)
    - Caesar, 1998 (Box 48)
    - As You Like It, 2010 (Box 48)
    - The Winter's Tale, 2012 (Box 48)
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream, 1986 (Box 48)
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream Costume, 1986 (Box 48)
      White dress with red swirls was costume for Helena.
    - King Lear Costume, 1987 (Box 48)
      Green dress and black cloak were costume for Goneril.
  - Oversize: Posters (Box 49)
    - All's Well That Ends Well (2) (Box 49)
    - King Lear, 2003 (Box 49)
    - Macbeth (Box 49)
    - The Merry Wives of Windsor (Box 49)
    - Romeo and Juliet (2), 1980 (Box 49)
    - The Tempest (Box 49)
    - The Winder's Tale, 1997 (Box 49)
    - The Winter's Tale (Box 49)
    - Much Ado About Nothing (Box 49)
    - Henry IV, Part I (Original and Copy) (Box 49)